Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Communist and Socialist Serials TAM.747
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: American Publications, 1881-2010; 68.4 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 102 flat boxes
  - Workers Revolution: League for the Revolutionary Party, 1990; cuid11903 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Communist: Internal Newsletter of the League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L): League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L), 1979; cuid11904 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Forward: League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L), San Francisco, CA, 1979-1980; cuid11905 (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
  - Unity / La Unidad: League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L), San Francisco, CA, 1977; cuid11906 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Study Guide for Mao Zedong's Theory of the Three Worlds: League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L)/Getting Together Publications, Oakland, CA, 1979; cuid11907 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Left Book Club News & Reviews: Left Book Club, Camp Hill, PA, 1982; cuid11908 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Left Opposition: Left Opposition, San Francisco, CA, 1996; cuid11909 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Leftward Ho!: Leftward Ho!, New York, NY, 1997; cuid11910 (Box 131, Folder 6, Box 228, Folder 16)
  - In Defense of Bolshevism: Leninist League, New York, NY, 1937; cuid11911 (Box 131, Folder 7, Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Split in the S.W.P.: Leninist League, New York, NY, 1940; cuid11912 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - What Hitler Wants: Leon Trotsky/ The John Day Company, New York, NY, 1933; cuid11913 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Liberal News: Liberal Party of New York State, New York, NY, 1959, 1963; cuid11914 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Where are We Now?: Liberation, New York, NY, 1956; cuid11915 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - 75 Years of Struggle: Liberator Press, Chicago, Il, 1975; cuid11916 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Revolutionary Movement in Spain: Libertarian Publishing Society, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid11917 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Monthly: Libertarian Socialist League, New York, NY, 1952; cuid11918 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - 5th National Conference: Liberation Socialist League, New York, NY, 1952 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Reading Labor Advocate: Local Berks County, Socialist Party, Reading, PA, 1958; cuid11919 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Jobs not Battleships!: Local New York, Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1940; cuid11920 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Class Struggle: for the Rebuilding of Fourth International: Lutte Ouvriere, 1972, 1974-1975; cuid11921 (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - ABC of Communism: Lyceum-Literature Department, Workers Party of America, New York, NY, 1919; cuid11922 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Creeping Socialist: Madison Local of the DSA, Madison, WI, 1984; cuid11923 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - 5th Annual Socialist Scholars Conference: Against Domination: State, Class, Race, and Gender (booklet): Manhattan Community College, CUNY, 1987; cuid11924 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - MIM Notes: Maoist International Movement, Los Angeles, CA, 1989-1995, 2000-2004; cuid11925 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Bolshevik: Mapta, 1948; cuid11926 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - New Life: A Socialist Bulletin Serving the Labor Party Movement: Margaret Guttshall, Detroit, MI, 1995-1996; cuid11927 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Pacific Maritime Worker: Maritime Unionists of the Pacific Coast, San Francisco, CA, 1938; cuid11928 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - We Only Want...The Earth!: Mark Manning, Seattle, WA, 1995; cuid11929 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Marxian: Marx Institute, Brooklyn. NY, 1919; cuid11930 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter: Marxist Education Collective, New York, NY, 1977; cuid11931 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts and Summary - Marxist Education Collective Second Conference: Marxist Education Collective, New York, NY, 1976; cuid11932 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Studies in Marxism 1: Marxism & new left ideology: Marxist Educational Press, Minneapolis, MN, 1977; cuid11933 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Red Flag: Marxist League, Hollywood, CA, 1937; cuid11934 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Marxist Worker: Marxist Workers Committee, New York, NY, 1979; cuid11935 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Spark: Marxist Workers League/Spark Publishers, Brooklyn, NY, 1939; cuid11936 (Box 94, Folder 2-3)
  - Communist Line: Marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee, 1975-1976; cuid11937 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Communist Line: marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee, San Francisco, CA, 1976; cuid11938 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Marxist-Leninist Research Bureau Report: Marxist-Leninist Resrarch Bureau, circa 1990s; cuid11939 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Voice against war and imperialism: marxist-Leninist Study Group, Chicago, IL, 1984; cuid11940 (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Worker: Marxist-Leninist Workers Organization, Chicago, IL, 1990; cuid11941 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Worker: Marxist-Leninist Workers Organization, Chicago, IL, 1989; cuid11942 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Indiana Socialist News: Mary Donovan Hapgood Local of the Socialist Party, USA, Indianapolis, IN, 1974; cuid11943 (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - I Speak My Own Piece: Masses & Mainstream, New York, NY, 1955; cuid11944 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - McCarthy Advance: McCarthy for President National Headquarters, Washington, DC, 1968; cuid11945 (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - NST: Nature, Society and Thought: MEP Publications, Minneapolis, MN, 1987-1989; cuid11946 (Box 112, Folder 4-6, Box 232, Folder 12-13)
  - Black Nationalism and Socialism: Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1968; cuid11947 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Fascism: What is it- How to fight it: Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11948 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Leon Trotsky on Engels and Kautsky: Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11949 (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - Marxist Theory of the State: Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11950 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Marxist Theory of the State: Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11951 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - On the Labor Party in the United States: Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11952 (Box 131, Folder 27)
  - On the Revolutionary Potential of the Working Class: Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11953 (Box 131, Folder 28)
  - Interntional Bulletin: Militant, 1945; cuid11954 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Communism and Syndicalism: Militant Press, New York, Ny, 1931; cuid11955 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - The Militant: The Militant Publishing Association, New York, NY, 1942, 1952; cuid13373 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Militant: Militant Publishing Association, Toronto, Canada, 1977; cuid13367 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Militant: Militant Publishing Association, New York, NY, 1942, 1952, 1956-1958, 1966, 1970- 1974, 1977, 1980, 1981, 1995; cuid13364 (Box 37, Folder 3, Box 186, Folder 3-7, Box 187, Folder 1-5, Box 188, Folder 1-4, Box 189)
  - Militant: the Marxist Paper for Labor and Youth: Militant Publishing Association, London, England, 1973, 1991; cuid13366 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Militant (index): Militant Publishing Association, New York, NY, 1991-1996; cuid13368 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Milwaukee Worker: Milwaukee Worker, Milwaukee, WI, 1973-1974; cuid11956 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter: Minneapolis Chapter New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1973; cuid11957 (Box 131, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter: Minnesota Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Minneapolis, MN, 1987; cuid11958 (Box 131, Folder 30)
  - Road to Peace: Minnesota Council of American-Soviet Friendship, New York, NY, 1990; cuid11959 (Box 131, Folder 31)
  - Zen-Marxism: Subjective Factors in Devising Revolutionary Strategy: Mitchel Cohen, Brooklyn, NY, 1987; cuid11960 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Modern Quarterly: A Journal of Radical Opinion: Modern Quarterly, New York, NY, 1938; cuid11961 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Review Press: Monthly Review, New York, NY/London, England, 1978-1979, 1983-1984; cuid11962 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Principles of Communism: Monthly Review, New York, NY, 1952; cuid11963 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - MR Sustainer's Newsletter: Monthly Review Foundation, New York, NY, 1987; cuid11964 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Review1: Monthly Review Inc., New York, NY, 1965; cuid11965 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Monthy Review: Monthly Review, Inc, New York, NY, 1934; cuid11966 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Jewish People Will Live On!: Morning Freiheit Association, New York, NY, 1944; cuid11967 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin: Morningside Heights Socialist Party, 1941; cuid11968 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter: Movement for a Democratic Society, 1969; cuid11969 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - New Flag/La Nueva Bandera: Movimiento Popular Peru in North America, Queens, NY, 1997; cuid11970 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - North America News Service: Digest of Revolutionary Journals from North America and Other Countries: N.F.C. Publications, Boston, MA, 1973; cuid11971 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - New York Marxist School: N.Y. Committee for Education, New York, NY, 1981-1982; cuid11972 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Rebel Voices: N.Y. Regional General Membership Branch of the Industrial Workers of the World (IWW), New York, NY, 1983; cuid11973 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Trotsky, Prince of Phamphleteers: Nation & The Athenaeum, 1922; cuid11974 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Footnote on an Historic Case: In Re Alger Hiss, No. 78 Civ. 3433: Nation Institute, New York, NY, 1983; cuid11975 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Policy: National Affairs, Inc., New York, NY, 1976-1977; cuid11976 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Fight for Recovery: National Campaign Committee for the Communist Party, New York, NY, 1938; cuid11977 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Strategy for Socialism volumes 1 and 2: National Caucus of Labor Committees, New York, NY, 1973-1974; cuid11978 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Strategy for Socialism: National Caucus of Labor Committees / The Campaigner, New York, NY, 1973; cuid11979 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Why Revolution: National Caucus of SDS Labor Committees, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid11980 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Impose Sanctions Now!: National Center for Trade Union Action and Democracy, Chicago, IL, circa 1940s; cuid11981 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee: Bulwark of Segregation: National Committe to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1963; cuid11982 (Box 132, Folder 16-17)
  - Internal Bulletin No. 13: national committee of the communist league of america (opposition), circa 1940s; cuid11983 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Information Bulletin: National Committee of the Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1982, 1984, 1985, 1986, 1988, 1989, 1990; cuid11984 (Box 133, Folder 1-4)
  - Free the Three: National Committee to Combat Fascism, Milwaukee, WI, circa 1970s; cuid11985 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Double-Barrelled Assault: Economic Crisis & the Gulf War: Report to the National Committee of the Communist Party, USA: National Committee, CPUSA, 1991; cuid11986 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Shall the Communist Party Change its Name?: National Committee, CPUSA, New York, NY, 1944; cuid11987 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Struggle against the economic crisis - Turn the Party outward: Report to the National Committee Communist Party, USA: National Committee, CPUSA, New York, NY, 1992; cuid11988 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - The Crisis in the Soviet Union: National Committee, CPUSA, 1991; cuid11989 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - The Crisis in Our Party: Report to the National Committee: National Committee, CPUSA, 1991; cuid11990 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - CPUSA: growth, action & leadership: National Committee/National Council CPUSA, New York, NY, 1988; cuid11991 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Anti Fascist Front: National Committees to Combat Fascism in America, Oakland, CA, 1969; cuid11992 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Forge Unity Through Struggle: National Convention, CPUSA, Cleveland, OH, 1991; cuid11993 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter: National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, New York, NY, 1943, 1950; cuid11994 (Box 133, Folder 12, Box 232, Folder 2)
  - "We Will Join Hands With Russia": National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc, New York, NY, 1943; cuid11995 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Organized Labor in the Soviet Union: National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc., New York, NY, 1944; cuid11996 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - The Truth About The Book the Nazis Like: National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc., New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid11997 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Super Profits and Crises: Modern US Capitalism: National Education Commission, CPUSA, 1988; cuid11998 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Economic Situation and the Struggle for Wages and Against Unemployment: Outline and Guide for Schools, Classes, Study Groups: National Education Department, Communist Party, New York, NY, 1949; cuid11999 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - ABC of Marxism: National Educational Department-Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid12000 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Bulletin of the Social Labor Movement: National Executive Committee of the Socialist Labor Party, Detroit, MI, 1881; cuid12001 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - An Open Letter to Activists of the Past and Present on the Need for A Mass Party of the People: National Interim Committee for a Mass Party of the People, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid12002 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Study Guide on the Jewish Question: National Jewish Commission of the Communist Party, New York, NY, 1946; cuid12003 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - Fist & Rose: National Office of the Socialist Party, USA, Milwaukee, WI, 1978; cuid12004 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Eugene Dennis Indicts the Wall Street Conspirators: National Office, Communist Party, New York, NY, 1948; cuid12005 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - New Times Call for a New Communist Youth Organization: National organizing Committee for a Communist Youth Organization, New York, NY, 1983; cuid12006 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Young Worker: National Organizing Committee for a Communist Youth Organization, New York, NY, 1983; cuid12007 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Rainbow Organizer: National Rainbow Coalition, Inc., Washington, DC, 1988; cuid12008 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - FrameUp: the opening defense statement made by Angela Y. Davis: National United Committee to Free Angela Davis, San Francisco, CA, 1972; cuid12009 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Freedom's Cause: Soviet Youth at War: New Age Publishers, New York, NY, 1943; cuid12010 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Review: New Age Publishers, New York, NY, 1940; cuid12011 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Who Are the Young Communists?: New Age Publishers, New York, NY, 1941; cuid12012 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Critical Times: New America Movement, Philadelphia, PA, 1974; cuid12013 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore NAM Newsletter: New American Movement, Baltimore, MD, 1980; cuid12014 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - East Bay Voice: New American Movement, 1979; cuid12015 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Gateway Star: New American Movement, St. Louis, MO, 1979; cuid12016 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Human Needs Report: New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1973; cuid12017 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Impeach Bulletin: New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1973; cuid12018 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Movin' On!: New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1973; cuid12019 (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - NAM [Assorted newsletters, correspondence, printed ephemera]: New American Movement, 1979, 1981; cuid12020 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - NAM Women's Newsletter: New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1972; cuid12021 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - New American Movement: New American Movement, Berkeley, CA, 1971-1976; cuid12022 (Box 88, Folder 1-7)
  - New American Movement Discussion Bulletin: New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1972; cuid12023 (Box 87, Folder 7, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Newsletter: New American Movement, 1975; cuid12024 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Political Perspective: New American Movement, Chicago, IL, 1978; cuid12025 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Political Perspectives of the New American Movement: New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1972; cuid12026 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Power Plays: New American Movement, circa 1970s; cuid12027 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Convention Papers 1975: New American Movement (Organization), cuid12028 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - New American Movement Energy Commission Newsletter: New American Movement Energy Commission, Urbana, IL, 1980; cuid12029 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - New Orleans Socialist Union: New American Movement New Orleans, New Orleans, LA, 1973; cuid12030 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - New American Movement Pittsburgh Chapter Newsletter: New American Movement Pittsburgh Chapter, Pittsburgh, PA, 1981; cuid12031 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Red Gargoyle: New American Movement, Southside Chapter, Chicago, IL, 1977; cuid12032 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Marxist Pamphlets No. 3 - United Front Against Fascism: New Century Publication, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12033 (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - American Way to Jobs, Peace, Democracy: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1954; cuid12034 (Box 134, Folder 22, Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Crisis in the Middle East: Which Way Israel?: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1956; cuid12035 (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - Draft Resolution for the 16th National Convention of the Communist Party, USA: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1956; cuid12036 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - End the Cold War: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1962; cuid12037 (Box 134, Folder 24)
  - Ideoloical Struggle in the American Left: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1963; cuid12038 (Box 134, Folder 25)
  - Only Choice: Peaceful Coexistence: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1963; cuid12039 (Box 134, Folder 26)
  - Reaction Beats its War Drums: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1946; cuid12040 (Box 134, Folder 27)
  - Red-Baiters Menace America: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1946; cuid12041 (Box 134, Folder 28)
  - Should Americans Back the Marshall Plan?: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1948; cuid12042 (Box 134, Folder 29)
  - Stool-pigeon: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1949; cuid12043 (Box 134, Folder 30)
  - The Soviet Union and World Peace: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1946; cuid12044 (Box 134, Folder 31)
  - Treatment of Defeated Germany: New Century Publishers, 1945; cuid12045 (Box 134, Folder 32)
  - Trotskyite 5th Column in the Labor Movement: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1945; cuid12046 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Women on Guard: How the Women of the World Fight for Peace: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1952; cuid12047 (Box 134, Folder 33)
  - San Francisco World Security Conference: Your Questions Answered: New Century Publishers, Inc., New York, NY, 1945; cuid12048 (Box 134, Folder 34)
  - American Way To Jobs - Peace - Democracy: New Century Publishers/CPUSA, New York, NY, 1954; cuid12049 (Box 134, Folder 35)
  - People United: New Dawn Party, Berkeley, CA, 1975; cuid12050 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - New Dawn: New Dawn Party - Marxist/Leninist, Berkeley, CA, 1975; cuid12051 (Box 134, Folder 36)
  - New Deal: New Deal Publishing Association, New York, NY, 1932; cuid12052 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - NDM National Bulletin: New Democratic Movement, Baltimore, MD, 1987; cuid12053 (Box 134, Folder 37)
  - Newsletter: New England Committees of Correspondence, 1985-1987; cuid12054 (Box 134, Folder 38)
  - Marxism and Black Radicalism in America: New England Free Press, Somerville, MA, 1971; cuid12055 (Box 134, Folder 39)
  - Stalin, Marxism-Leninism and the Left: New England Free Press, Somerville, MA, 1976; cuid12056 (Box 134, Folder 40)
  - New Foundations [and supplement]: New Foundations, New York, NY, 1952; cuid12057 (Box 134, Folder 41)
  - Socialism: The Hope of Humanity: New International Publishing Co./Workers Party of the United States, New York, NY, 1942; cuid12058 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - New Left Forum: new Left Forum, Binghamton, NY, 1968; cuid12059 (Box 134, Folder 42)
  - New Marxist Forum: New Marxist Foru, Bronx, NY, 1973; cuid12060 (Box 134, Folder 43)
  - Road for Revolutionary Socialists: new Militant Publishing, New York, NY, 1936; cuid12061 (Box 134, Folder 44)
  - Louisiana Worker: New Orleans Socialist Union, New Orleans, LA, 1973; cuid12062 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Colonial Plunder of Puerto Rico: New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY, 1972; cuid12063 (Box 134, Folder 45)
  - Cuban Revolultion, National Liberation, and the Soviet Union: New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY, 1974; cuid12064 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - End Fascist Terror and US Imperialism in Chile: New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY, 1974; cuid12065 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Meaning of San Rafael: New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY, 1971; cuid12066 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - The Communist Party and How It Works: A Handbook on its Organization and Functioning: New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY, 1976; cuid12067 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - What Happened in Poland: New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12068 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - New Unionist: New Union Party, Minneapolis, MN, 1982; cuid12069 (Box 135, Folder 6, Box Shared Tamiment 062, Folder 14, Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 14-17, Box Shared Tamiment 063, Folder 1-10)
  - New Voice: New Voice, Sacramento, CA, 1974, 1977; cuid12070 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - New Voice: New Voice, Sacramento, CA, 1974-1984; cuid12071 (Box 157, Folder 11-12)
  - New York DSOC News Bulletin: New York Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1976; cuid12072 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Socialist: New York Democratic Socialists of America, New York, NY, 1985; cuid12073 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - New York City Democratic Socialists of America: New York Democratic Socialists of America, New York, NY, 1993; cuid12074 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - NY DSA Monthly Newsletter: New York Deomcratic Socialists of America, New York, NY, 1986-1987; cuid12075 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Independent Socialist: New York Independent Socialist Club, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid12076 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Independent Socialist: New York Independent Socialist Club, New York, NY, 1967-1969; cuid12077 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Philosophy of Socialist Education: New York Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12078 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - A Socialist in Congress: New York Labor News, Palo Alto, CA, 1962; cuid12079 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Capitalism and Unemployment: New York Labor News, New York, NY, 1976; cuid12080 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Reform or Revolution: New York Labor News, Palo Alto, CA, 1974; cuid12081 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Reconstruction of Society: New York Labor News, Brooklyn, NY, 1930, 1968; cuid12082 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Why is capitalism running out of gas?: New York Labor News, Palo Alto, CA, 1977; cuid12083 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Karl Marx, the Man: New York Labor News Co., New York, NY, 1926; cuid12084 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Reviling of the Great: New York Labor News Co./Socialist Labor Party, New York, NY, 1949; cuid12085 (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Bourgeois Revolution: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1955; cuid12086 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - Daniel de Leon Internationalist: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1944; cuid12087 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Daniel De Leon: Disciplinarian: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1943; cuid12088 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Free Trade: An Address Delivered...: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1921; cuid12089 (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - Gotha Program: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12090 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - Historical Materialism: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1928; cuid12091 (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - Industrial Unionism: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12092 (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - Revolutionary Act: Military Insurrection or Political and Economic Action?: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1922; cuid12093 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Socialism and Human Nature: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1944; cuid12094 (Box 135, Folder 26)